( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 24=
Talking work?
I came at a bad time, then.
Here for Gu Yan?
Sorry to intrude.
I'll come back later.
My wedding is in two days.
Zhou Mei agreed to be my bridesmaid.
I hope you can make it, too.
I know I always steal your resources
and your people.
But our rivalry kept me going.
Honestly, just thinking
that Colorful Culture Media
could beat Chenxing
is motivation.
You used to doubt Ling Yikai and me.
Now, I've proven you wrong.
I did it.
Congratulations.
You made it.
I'll be there.
Thank you.
I have a question.
What is it?
Who is Sansan?
A new author I signed.
Is it Gu Yan?
No.
(Which of these books
and drafts do you want to keep?)
(I'll leave them at the front desk.)
(Otherwise, I'll get rid of them.)
Are you moving?
It's not the first time.
The best part about living in hotels is
that when you get sick of one,
you can just move to another.
Where are you moving?
Somewhere with a bit more culture.
I'll come see you after work.
Wait for me.
(Tianyi Games: About Us)
Sorry for making you all work overtime.
Hello.
- Ms. Lin.
It's no problem.
I just explained
the situation to the team.
They're playing hardball, so be ready.
Let's get started, then.
Okay.
Tianyi Games
has developed many projects
since its founding in 2015.
Take "Wildfire",
a major game they made years ago.
It's still a hit.
I'm sure you all know it.
Their founder, Mr. Kun,
(Kun Zhida)
is actually a fan of He Han's work.
Two years ago,
they approached us about
the adaptation rights
for "Tao Yao: Dream of Wuchuan".
But their proposal failed to
capture the essence of the novel,
so the deal fell through.
So now,
they're basically
reviving an old proposal.
The most infuriating part is
that the proposal is
the same as it was two years ago.
They didn't even
bother changing the date.
They just lowered the licensing fee.
Kicking us while we're down.
Mr. Kun claims
he has a last-minute trip next week.
So he can only see us tomorrow,
and only for two hours in the afternoon.
How else would he show off
how much money he makes?
True.
It's a compliance test.
By sitting here today,
we've already started the negotiation.
He's trying to gain the upper hand
to make us back down.
Our goal today
is to establish our bottom line
and devise a counter-strategy.
Mr. He.
Sorry to bother you.
It's okay. Come in.
Would you mind
settling this bill?
Your previous balance
has already been cleared,
and the deposit was refunded.
The invoice was sent to your email.
So for this extra charge...
No problem.
I'm really sorry for the trouble.
Don't be sorry.
I should be thanking you
for taking care of me.
It's my pleasure.
Hold on.
A sponsor gave me this model sports car.
I think your son might like it.
Mr. He, this is too generous.
I can't accept it.
Please, take it.
Do you need anything else, Mr. He?
Like packing or booking a car...
- Or...
- No, I'm good.
Alright. I'll see you off tomorrow.
Never mind.
You see off so many guests every day.
One less won't matter.
Understood, Mr. He.
- Go back to work.
- I'll get going.
Here we go.
Food's here.
Pass it around.
Even though we're working late,
we still need
to keep our nutrition up.
Here, pass this.
Thanks.
- Get some Vitamin C.
- Thanks.
Here.
- Come on. Help yourselves.
- Vitamin C.
Come on.
- Thanks.
- This is for you.
Eat first. I'm not hungry.
Ms. Lin, you have dinner plans tonight?
Look at the time.
More like a midnight snack.
Just eat your food.
Now,
I'll walk you through it while you eat.
Adapting supporting characters is fine.
But the main characters must follow
our character bios.
The style is still based on
"Wildfire".
Because that's his comfort zone.
But to us,
it feels like a forced mashup.
Ms. Lin,
isn't he a fan of He Han?
Why is he demanding such big changes?
Fundamentally, I think
what he really wants to make
is "Tao Yao of Wildfire."
So he wants to force his personal mark
onto "Tao Yao: Dream of Wuchuan."
Mr. Kun's assistant just messaged.
They asked the Chenxing team
to do some homework
before tomorrow's meeting
and familiarize ourselves
with "Wildfire."
Here's the intro for "Wildfire."
Should I cast it?
Yes.
Put it up. Let's see.
They also want us to focus
on the player comments section.
It's right here.
This includes feedback on characters,
plotlines, and level design.
They want us to read through it.
They want us to...
Did they send this, too?
Mr. Kun wants us
to see
their status among players
and understand their strengths.
Pure narcissism.
Come in half an hour early tomorrow.
Thanks, everyone.
Got it, Ms. Lin.
- Got it.
- Okay, Ms. Lin.
At your hotel in five minutes.
Hello, Miss.
How can I help you?
Hi, where is Mr. He?
He checked out.
He left a few minutes ago.
Hello, Ms. Lin.
Mr. He left this for you.
Are you taking it all?
I'll take it all. Thanks.
Okay.
♪For first love♪
(You've retracted a message.)
(He Han)
♪It was a constant pursuit♪
♪Yet no one ever knew♪
♪For so long♪
♪I longed to be with you♪
♪And you finally appeared♪
♪Calling my name in the air♪
♪Waiting with open arms♪
♪I see you at the end♪
♪Now I cross the line♪
Sent.
♪Just to love and be with you♪
Discarded a five, and drew a six.
♪Now I cross the line♪
♪Just to love and be with you♪
♪Love♪
♪Cause now I see you there♪
♪Waiting with open arms♪
♪I see you at the end♪
♪Now I cross the line♪
♪Just to love and be with you♪
♪Call my name♪
♪Here we are♪
♪I'm waiting for long♪
♪Stay where you are♪
♪I will come to you♪
♪I'll never let you go♪
Are you asleep?
I'm downstairs.
Hello?
Why are you here so late?
Nothing.
I met up with a friend.
I didn't want to go home,
so I came to see you.
It's late.
Did I disturb you?
It's fine.
I was replying to emails.
About the divorce...
I've brought it up with my wife.
I'm not joking around.
And it's not on a whim.
I've been waiting for the right moment.
And this seems like the best time.
When things are going badly for me,
proposing to split our assets
might be easier for her to accept.
What did she say?
Shocked.
Surprised.
She needs time to process it.
Give me a little more time.
Okay?
It won't be long.
Mrs. Bei was worried
that Lawyer Bei might
get dragged into other messes.
Using asset planning as an excuse,
she asked Lawyer Bei for a divorce.
In every possible way,
Lawyer Bei is against it.
But it's hard to save yourself.
Even for lawyers.
Mrs. Bei didn't do this on a whim.
She came prepared.
A model couple in public,
but behind closed doors,
only they know the truth.
Why are you smiling?
Because life is unpredictable.
Has Zhang Yousen looked for you lately?
No.
Are you new here?
Come here.
Sir, what do you do?
I'm the king of stories.
What about you?
Jun, you're going to be late for school!
For you.
Bye, Sir.
Heading out?
(Zhanqiao: Where did you move to?)
Hello, Mr. Kun.
Lin Zhanqiao.
After you.
How are you still in this dump?
The same shabby storefront.
Fix it.
If we work together,
my first task
will be to expand this office for you.
Or we could move it.
How about that?
Hello, Mr. Kun.
Mantou, take Mr. Kun inside.
I need to take this call. Sorry.
This way, Mr. Kun.
Right this way.
Hello, Mr. Kun.
Please, come in.
This way.
Please.
- Have a seat.
- Hello?
Right this way.
Did you get the books?
Where did you move to?
Send me your address.
I need to see you about something.
Okay.
What you just pitched
is how you handle online fiction.
Games have their own rules.
Understand?
My last game had
over 100 million downloads.
Hundreds of millions in monthly traffic.
Can you do that?
Who?
Your best online fiction,
even He Han's novel...
How big of an audience can you reach?
How big?
We are in completely different leagues.
Understand?
I want to buy
"Tao Yao: Dream of Wuchuan".
And the only reason
I'm here talking to you
is that I'm a loyal fan of He Han.
Understand?
I know exactly how to turn his story
into a better game.
You guys don't.
You don't know.
Lin Zhanqiao certainly doesn't know.
Don't you guys need money?
Our company has plenty of it.
Take the money.
Then, stay out of the rest.
Mr. Kun
is impossible to talk to.
What he wants is
a co-branded game with He Han.
And at the same time,
erase our involvement entirely.
Let's wait and see for now.
Unless we're out of options,
we need to keep our pride.
Should I take you back now?
Actually...
Drop me off at Siwei Apartments.
Okay.
Siwei Apartments.
Ms. Lin.
Come in.
Tell me.
Why are you here?
Or did you just want to soak in
the cultural atmosphere here?
I wanted to ask you
about your future plans.
I haven't decided.
Need a drink?
I'm ordering delivery.
I'm good.
Just order for yourself.
Two Americanos.
Things aren't going well on my end.
A shortage of new authors?
There's no one we can use.
What about your pillar,
Gu Yan?
What if I told you that Sansan,
who's writing the sequel
to "Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui,"
is actually Gu Yan?
It's a breach of contract.
I don't have proof.
I believe Zhao Lanxin
already talked to him.
So the contract and payments
are routed through someone else.
But why? Just for the money?
Probably a lack of security.
His debut was late,
and you've
overshadowed him as a legend.
That has nothing to do with me.
Maybe you didn't
give him enough security.
Maybe he feels
that if he ever became useless,
you'd just toss him aside.
So he had to find a backup plan.
He had to
prove he's better than everyone else.
Can Zhao Lanxin give him security?
He doesn't care about Zhao Lanxin.
Security isn't an issue.
"Parting with Yan Dan
at Yishui" by Sansan
is currently ranking higher
most of the time
than Gu Yan's own work,
"Drunk Old Friend."
I can understand why.
It's probably due to
- the Phantom Knight's hype.
- Lin Zhanqiao.
What are you trying to say?
I want you back at Chenxing.
I can't.
I really can't find a better author.
I need you back.
We can develop a new project together.
And then,
I'll talk to Mr. Fan.
What project?
I haven't figured it out yet.
When will you?
I don't think staying here alone
will change anything.
What are you running from?
Dai Shan is gone.
Things are tense
between you and Mr. Fan.
You need someone
to help you handle the fallout,
so you can fully focus
on a new project, right?
So you want me back at Chenxing
because you think I still need you.
Your life and your writing
have hit a major bottleneck.
You aren't a god.
Why won't you admit it?
You're just like everyone else.
Everyone goes through rough patches.
There's no shame in admitting it.
Accepting help from others isn't...
Thanks for the gesture, Lin Zhanqiao.
But I don't need it.
You just said it yourself.
The company has so many issues.
It's overwhelming.
So don't let me add to your burden.
Let's handle our own problems.
Hello. Your delivery is here.
I hope you can do as you said
and actually solve your own problems.
When that time comes,
I'll buy you that coffee.
Hello?
Are you sleeping?
I'm picking up my parents now
to take them to their hotel.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll pick up your grandma.
Makeup starts at 8:30 AM.
Get here around 9:00 AM.
Don't be late.
Mei.
Are you going to Zhao Lanxin's hotel
first thing tomorrow?
Yeah, I'm her bridesmaid.
So her best friend is actually you?
She doesn't have any other friends.
She's always alone.
Once she's married, she won't be.
On the surface, sure.
But in reality,
she's still alone.
(Lift)
Let's go, Mom.
I've booked your rooms.
We can head straight up from the garage.
One room each.
Next door to each other.
Next door is good.
Yes.
This way.
Dad, this room is yours.
Okay.
Mom, yours is next door.
Alright.
Get some rest.
Here, this one is yours.
Is your bridal suite here, too?
It's at the end of the hall.
Are you staying here tonight?
It was decorated this afternoon.
I'll leave it as is.
Head back, then.
Get some rest.
Okay.
Good night.
Mom.
Ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Lanxin, when is breakfast?
- I'm starving.
- Right now.
Let's wait for Dad.
- What is it?
- Let's go.
Hurry up.
- Time for breakfast.
- Already?
I haven't shaved yet.
It's fine.
Do it when we come back up.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
The buffet is on the fourth floor.
Give them your room number.
Okay.
Alright.
You guys go eat.
I'll head back to the suite.
Hello, Zhou Mei.
You're here?
Okay, I'll come down and get you.
(Mengtong Internet Cafe)
- Two boxes, right?
- Yes.
Heading to work?
Yeah.
Check this food order.
Alright.
I'm taking off.
Thanks.
Take care.
Why are you here?
I need to show you something.
I don't need anything.
I'm already making adjustments.
We'll talk once I finish writing.
It's not about "Drunk Old Friend".
Then what is it?
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui".
Even though
Phantom Knight didn't finish it,
authors always like to prepare
their character bios and outlines.
(2019 "Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui")
They even establish the lore in advance.
("Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui"
Project Plan)
(Ten Hours Ago)
Hello?
About Gu Yan ghostwriting for Sansan,
I thought of a way
to give him a warning.
The synopsis and world-building
of Phantom Knight's
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui"
are with you.
(2019 0818 "Parting with Yan Dan
at Yishui" Plot Outline)
("Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui"
Project Plan)
(Author: Phantom Knight.
Editor in Charge: Ma Zi'ang)
These files are from 2019.
Are you saying
Phantom Knight finished it long ago?
Believe it or not.
How did you get this?
Coincidence.
You're Phantom Knight?
Mr. Fan said
you started out writing novels
before switching to editing.
I can't believe
you're actually Phantom Knight.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
And since the synopsis for
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui"
was done,
why did you stop writing?
So you are Sansan.
I'm not.
Then, I'm not Phantom Knight.
Why give this to me?
If you aren't Sansan,
or you don't know him,
then after reading this synopsis,
just treat it as light reading.
But if you are Sansan,
to cover your tracks
and keep me from suspecting you,
after reading this,
unless you can write
something even better,
you'll have to forget it to avoid
similarities.
But for you,
that won't be easy.
Take your time.
I'm going to Zhao Lanxin's wedding.
(2019 "Parting with Yan Dan
at Yishui" Lore)
This way.
The watch
is in the car.
I'll get it.
Okay.
Ling Yikai.
Ling Yikai!
Who is it?
Get dressed and get out.
You're early.
No rush.
What do you want?
I should be asking you.
Are you mad?
Of course you are.
It's our wedding day.
And this is our bridal suite.
Yet you walk in on me
while I'm in bed with her.
You did it on purpose?
I wouldn't call it intentional.
I've always been like this.
You know that.
It's not too late to back out.
You don't have to marry me.
Save yourself.
You just want to gross me out,
hoping I can't stomach it
and let you go?
Keep dreaming.
Today is my big day.
No one is going to ruin it.
Not even you, Ling Yikai.
Why force this?
Must we both lose?
Do you think
living every day at each other's throats
is sustainable?
First, I haven't lost.
Second,
who doesn't
grit their teeth through life?
So,
I will make sure
everything goes according to my plan.
Are you insane?
Judging by this morning,
you're the insane one.
You drove me to it.
Everyone sees how good I am to you.
I gave up my career
and sold my house for you.
I took care of your grandmother.
And on our wedding day,
I have to endure your
cheating and betrayal.
I'll give you two choices.
You either leave now,
or stay for the banquet.
I'll save you a seat.
Are you insane?
Ling Yikai.
I'm taking my parents to get changed
before the videographer arrives.
Go take a shower
and scrub yourself clean.
Put on your suit.
Once my makeup is done
and my dress is on,
we serve tea
to my parents and your grandmother.
Happy wedding day.
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪